<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Seducing - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/seducing/</link>
    <description>Seducing - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/seducing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UQ - Pete Wei scams for sex, money, and emotional manipulation.</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This story is about a man named Pete Wei, who is a fraudster. He uses deception, blackmail, and emotional manipulation to scam girls. He has even studied pre-university courses and has targeted girls in Shenzhen and Australia. This story reveals the modern urban pitfalls of deception and fraud, and serves as a reminder for girls to be more aware and protective of themselves.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - Brisbane Business School girl&#39;s time management secrets</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article reveals the time management secrets of a 19-year-old girl from UQ Business School who is skilled in perfectly controlling the time relationship between her two boyfriends. She can switch between the two men and accurately balance their time. Her management experience can help you become a time management master and better handle your time in your daily life.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Soton - Sun* Hao, No Love in the UK</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:02:51 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[In this incident, a male student with the last name Sun successfully demonstrated the phrase "there is no love in the UK". Without the prompt from a dream, we may never know how many times this pure love warrior has fallen. The following is the chat record, which is also evidence of the male protagonist's ugly face.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - Bull God of Genitalia, Midnight Bull Attack</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A series of chat records exposed the harassment behavior of the Sydney Bull God brother among multiple women. The Bull God brother claimed to have professional skills in multiple fields, but often changed his identity and education background to deceive women with lies and false promises. At the same time, the Bull God brother also tried to get resourceful male students to invite him into the Sydney Rich Second Generation group and claimed to have assets in the United States. This behavior is very dangerous and should be widely concerned by society.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>TUoS - Kan Bowen&#39;s Seduction, Debt, and Slander</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 10:12:29 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[During the 10 months of dating Kan Bowen, the author experienced various forms of torture from this man. Kan Bowen borrowed money from the author and constantly slandered her, even attacking and spreading malicious rumors about her after the breakup. In terms of money, the author paid nearly 100,000 RMB for Kan Bowen and there is a dispute that cannot be resolved. This article exposes Kan Bowen's crimes and the harm suffered by his girlfriend, and discusses this immoral behavior that violates personal property and mental health.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Luo Junzhe&#39;s multiple illegal behaviors exposed</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:11:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Luo Junzhe's multiple illegal and unethical behaviors have been exposed, including stealing roommates' cash and credit cards, abusing cats, hiring prostitutes, freeloading, overcharging everyone, etc. He also set up his friend's online banking account to regularly transfer money to him, which is illegal and fraudulent to his friend. He also secretly used game cheats to deceive in games.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
