<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Girl - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/girl/</link>
    <description>Girl - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:33:14 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/girl/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UK - Exposing D&#39;s Lies and Slanders</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-cornwall-girl-d/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:33:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-cornwall-girl-d/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article comprehensively analyzes the lies and slanders of an ex-girlfriend, systematically exposing her acts of rumormongering, fraud, slander, etc., and responding to her accusations one by one to clarify the truth.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UoB - Wang Tiange Cyberbullying, Slander, and Reckless Infringement</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uob-wang-tiange/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:27:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uob-wang-tiange/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes the unethical behavior of a 93-year-old woman who recklessly violates the privacy of others, spreads rumors, and is subjected to doxxing on the internet. The author, based on personal experience, describes how the woman used screenshots, posted photos on social media, and doxxing to harass others, causing tremendous psychological pressure and serious mental and physical harm to the victims. At the same time, this article calls for serious crackdowns on cyberbullying and slander to protect the legitimate rights and dignity of every individual.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - Brisbane Business School girl&#39;s time management secrets</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article reveals the time management secrets of a 19-year-old girl from UQ Business School who is skilled in perfectly controlling the time relationship between her two boyfriends. She can switch between the two men and accurately balance their time. Her management experience can help you become a time management master and better handle your time in your daily life.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UM - Demon King accused of misconduct, but allegations are questionable</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:04:10 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article describes a Melbourne University student, Demon King, who has been accused of multiple violations, including physical assault and traffic violations. However, the allegations are questionable, and some descriptions are false. The origin and authenticity of the article have been questioned, causing a lot of controversy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UK - Anonymous Man cheated on multiple occasions and constantly cheated on</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-wzj/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 09:18:47 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-wzj/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A man lived with his ex-girlfriend WZY in Shanghai, who cheated on him multiple times and was constantly unfaithful. When the man returned to the UK to reunite with her, he saw that his ex-girlfriend and her former boyfriend had been playing together during the Spring Festival, and what happened between them was unknown. He wanted to try to continue his relationship with his ex-girlfriend in the UK, but found that she had already been in contact with other people. As the relationship developed and disintegrated, the man detailed his experiences with his ex-girlfriend in this article, including her constant cheating and deception, and the reasons for their final breakup. At the same time, the man also pointed out his ex-girlfriend's twisted values and improper motherly education.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - Wang Zhengtai controversy over unpaid rent and photography fees</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-zhen-taiwang/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 16:40:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-zhen-taiwang/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[International student Wang Zhengtai did not pay the remaining rent during the rental period, nor did she pay for the retouching fees. At the same time, she also showed a spoiled image on social media and allowed photographers to freeload. These behaviors have caused strong controversy and discussion on social media. The report exposes these negative behaviors and calls on international students to establish correct concepts of renting and interpersonal communication.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Yan Yuqi (Drug, Child Abuse, Extortion)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-yuqiyann/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:50:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-yuqiyann/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes Yan Yuqi, a foreign female student who left her own son in a room filled with oxygen tanks and a urine pool to go on a date to eat sea urchins, resulting in the child starving to death. Ms. Yan, in desperation, extorted her ex-boyfriend C, demanding that he handle her troubles in the US, including apartment fines, moving and cleaning fees, and luggage fees. She eventually threatened C with verbal abuse if he did not pay.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
