<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>US - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/us/</link>
    <description>US - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/us/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Green Hat Guy sparks controversy on campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:38:20 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[During the inquiry session of the online master's program at UCSD Rady School of Management, a Chinese girl's camera was turned on, showing her having sex with a boy. Subsequently, a man claiming to be "Green Hat Guy" broke the news on a series of gossip groups, forums, and Xiaohongshu, revealing a large number of students' sexual photos and videos, causing a huge uproar. This event has attracted widespread attention and condemnation both inside and outside the school, while also revealing different voices and complex interpersonal relationships within the campus.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>NYU - Wang Zicong Multiple Accusations (Fraud, Abuse, Deception)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-wang-zicong/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:57:35 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-wang-zicong/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Multiple accusations have been made against a man named Wang Zicong, including fabricating virtual friends to scam money, abusing pets, slandering ex-girlfriends, spreading rumors about abortions, and threatening domestic violence. In addition, he enjoys engaging in various illicit activities such as leaking girls' private photos and secretly filming them. His crimes are serious and require legal sanctions and punishment.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Luo Junzhe&#39;s multiple illegal behaviors exposed</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:11:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Luo Junzhe's multiple illegal and unethical behaviors have been exposed, including stealing roommates' cash and credit cards, abusing cats, hiring prostitutes, freeloading, overcharging everyone, etc. He also set up his friend's online banking account to regularly transfer money to him, which is illegal and fraudulent to his friend. He also secretly used game cheats to deceive in games.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>NYU - Andrew Zhao exposed for six bad behaviors</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-andrew-zhao/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:10:45 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-andrew-zhao/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes the heinous acts of Andrew Zhao, including secretly filming and disseminating photos of female students at New York University, spreading malicious rumors, and committing violence against his girlfriend. His moral bottom line is extremely low, he does not respect women, and he treats women as objects. Therefore, international students need to be vigilant, cautious in making friends, and protect their privacy and personal safety.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Yan Yuqi (Drug, Child Abuse, Extortion)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-yuqiyann/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:50:24 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-yuqiyann/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes Yan Yuqi, a foreign female student who left her own son in a room filled with oxygen tanks and a urine pool to go on a date to eat sea urchins, resulting in the child starving to death. Ms. Yan, in desperation, extorted her ex-boyfriend C, demanding that he handle her troubles in the US, including apartment fines, moving and cleaning fees, and luggage fees. She eventually threatened C with verbal abuse if he did not pay.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
