<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sex - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/sex/</link>
    <description>Sex - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/sex/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>QUB - Tang Shengxiang, Prince Beffa, and the Record of a Playboy</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/qub-prince-slogan/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:44:07 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/qub-prince-slogan/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A missing person notice led to the Queen's University Belfast landlord searching for Prince Beffa, who breached the contract and disappeared. Prince Beffa used deception and speculation to accumulate wealth, and had a notorious reputation. The record documents a series of events, including his story with his (ex-)girlfriend. Due to the girlfriend leaving her passport and reporting to the police, the police were called multiple times. Prince Beffa's poor English couldn't explain things clearly, and the police took him away.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Green Hat Guy sparks controversy on campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:38:20 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[During the inquiry session of the online master's program at UCSD Rady School of Management, a Chinese girl's camera was turned on, showing her having sex with a boy. Subsequently, a man claiming to be "Green Hat Guy" broke the news on a series of gossip groups, forums, and Xiaohongshu, revealing a large number of students' sexual photos and videos, causing a huge uproar. This event has attracted widespread attention and condemnation both inside and outside the school, while also revealing different voices and complex interpersonal relationships within the campus.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>KCL - Xing Lecong accused of sexual harassment and fraud</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:41:19 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Xing Lecong has been repeatedly accused of deceiving women under the guise of dating, and his behavior was monotonous, including attempts to touch them after being rejected. Multiple women have publicly exposed Xing Lecong's behavior, including one woman who detailed her experience. After being exposed, Xing Lecong continues to threaten and intimidate the parties involved. The incident is currently under investigation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - Bull God of Genitalia, Midnight Bull Attack</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A series of chat records exposed the harassment behavior of the Sydney Bull God brother among multiple women. The Bull God brother claimed to have professional skills in multiple fields, but often changed his identity and education background to deceive women with lies and false promises. At the same time, the Bull God brother also tried to get resourceful male students to invite him into the Sydney Rich Second Generation group and claimed to have assets in the United States. This behavior is very dangerous and should be widely concerned by society.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
