<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Harassment - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/harassment/</link>
    <description>Harassment - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/harassment/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UQ - Pete Wei scams for sex, money, and emotional manipulation.</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This story is about a man named Pete Wei, who is a fraudster. He uses deception, blackmail, and emotional manipulation to scam girls. He has even studied pre-university courses and has targeted girls in Shenzhen and Australia. This story reveals the modern urban pitfalls of deception and fraud, and serves as a reminder for girls to be more aware and protective of themselves.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UM - Demon King accused of misconduct, but allegations are questionable</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:04:10 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article describes a Melbourne University student, Demon King, who has been accused of multiple violations, including physical assault and traffic violations. However, the allegations are questionable, and some descriptions are false. The origin and authenticity of the article have been questioned, causing a lot of controversy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>KCL - Xing Lecong accused of sexual harassment and fraud</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:41:19 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Xing Lecong has been repeatedly accused of deceiving women under the guise of dating, and his behavior was monotonous, including attempts to touch them after being rejected. Multiple women have publicly exposed Xing Lecong's behavior, including one woman who detailed her experience. After being exposed, Xing Lecong continues to threaten and intimidate the parties involved. The incident is currently under investigation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - Bull God of Genitalia, Midnight Bull Attack</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A series of chat records exposed the harassment behavior of the Sydney Bull God brother among multiple women. The Bull God brother claimed to have professional skills in multiple fields, but often changed his identity and education background to deceive women with lies and false promises. At the same time, the Bull God brother also tried to get resourceful male students to invite him into the Sydney Rich Second Generation group and claimed to have assets in the United States. This behavior is very dangerous and should be widely concerned by society.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
