<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Infidelity - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/infidelity/</link>
    <description>Infidelity - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/infidelity/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - Brisbane Business School girl&#39;s time management secrets</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article reveals the time management secrets of a 19-year-old girl from UQ Business School who is skilled in perfectly controlling the time relationship between her two boyfriends. She can switch between the two men and accurately balance their time. Her management experience can help you become a time management master and better handle your time in your daily life.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UK - Chen Bangrui&#39;s exceptional time management skills and emotional manipulation</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-chen-bangrui/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:25:28 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-chen-bangrui/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[The girl in the article developed feelings for Chen Bangrui during their six-month relationship, but was informed by him one night that he had a girlfriend in the UK and asked her to fly to the UK to be with him immediately. After being deceived, she was attacked on the phone by a stranger and fell into pain and despair. The article also includes a conversation record with the girlfriend.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Green Hat Guy sparks controversy on campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:38:20 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-oh-my-gosh/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[During the inquiry session of the online master's program at UCSD Rady School of Management, a Chinese girl's camera was turned on, showing her having sex with a boy. Subsequently, a man claiming to be "Green Hat Guy" broke the news on a series of gossip groups, forums, and Xiaohongshu, revealing a large number of students' sexual photos and videos, causing a huge uproar. This event has attracted widespread attention and condemnation both inside and outside the school, while also revealing different voices and complex interpersonal relationships within the campus.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>KCL - Xing Lecong accused of sexual harassment and fraud</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:41:19 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/kcl-xing-lecong/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Xing Lecong has been repeatedly accused of deceiving women under the guise of dating, and his behavior was monotonous, including attempts to touch them after being rejected. Multiple women have publicly exposed Xing Lecong's behavior, including one woman who detailed her experience. After being exposed, Xing Lecong continues to threaten and intimidate the parties involved. The incident is currently under investigation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Soton - Sun* Hao, No Love in the UK</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:02:51 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[In this incident, a male student with the last name Sun successfully demonstrated the phrase "there is no love in the UK". Without the prompt from a dream, we may never know how many times this pure love warrior has fallen. The following is the chat record, which is also evidence of the male protagonist's ugly face.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>TUoS - Kan Bowen&#39;s Seduction, Debt, and Slander</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 10:12:29 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[During the 10 months of dating Kan Bowen, the author experienced various forms of torture from this man. Kan Bowen borrowed money from the author and constantly slandered her, even attacking and spreading malicious rumors about her after the breakup. In terms of money, the author paid nearly 100,000 RMB for Kan Bowen and there is a dispute that cannot be resolved. This article exposes Kan Bowen's crimes and the harm suffered by his girlfriend, and discusses this immoral behavior that violates personal property and mental health.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UK - Anonymous Man cheated on multiple occasions and constantly cheated on</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-wzj/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 09:18:47 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-wzj/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A man lived with his ex-girlfriend WZY in Shanghai, who cheated on him multiple times and was constantly unfaithful. When the man returned to the UK to reunite with her, he saw that his ex-girlfriend and her former boyfriend had been playing together during the Spring Festival, and what happened between them was unknown. He wanted to try to continue his relationship with his ex-girlfriend in the UK, but found that she had already been in contact with other people. As the relationship developed and disintegrated, the man detailed his experiences with his ex-girlfriend in this article, including her constant cheating and deception, and the reasons for their final breakup. At the same time, the man also pointed out his ex-girlfriend's twisted values and improper motherly education.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>YU - Chen Yu Jian (Domestic Violence, Hypocrisy, PUA)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/yu-chen-yujian/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:07:11 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/yu-chen-yujian/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes a modern love tragedy that comes at the cost of false promises. The girl was deceived into a trap by a married man. The story she describes is full of pain and heartbreak, as she has been forgiving of him but he only cares about his own feelings. The behavior of a married man has caused her to experience domestic violence and emotional harm. This story is poignant because many people have similar experiences in real life. This article provides a reflective thinking, revealing the inequality and intricate emotional web in modern male-female relationships.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Luo Junzhe&#39;s multiple illegal behaviors exposed</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:11:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uscd-david/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Luo Junzhe's multiple illegal and unethical behaviors have been exposed, including stealing roommates' cash and credit cards, abusing cats, hiring prostitutes, freeloading, overcharging everyone, etc. He also set up his friend's online banking account to regularly transfer money to him, which is illegal and fraudulent to his friend. He also secretly used game cheats to deceive in games.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
