<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>USYD - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/usyd/</link>
    <description>USYD - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/usyd/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>USYD - Bull God of Genitalia, Midnight Bull Attack</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A series of chat records exposed the harassment behavior of the Sydney Bull God brother among multiple women. The Bull God brother claimed to have professional skills in multiple fields, but often changed his identity and education background to deceive women with lies and false promises. At the same time, the Bull God brother also tried to get resourceful male students to invite him into the Sydney Rich Second Generation group and claimed to have assets in the United States. This behavior is very dangerous and should be widely concerned by society.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - Wang Zhengtai controversy over unpaid rent and photography fees</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-zhen-taiwang/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 16:40:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/usyd-zhen-taiwang/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[International student Wang Zhengtai did not pay the remaining rent during the rental period, nor did she pay for the retouching fees. At the same time, she also showed a spoiled image on social media and allowed photographers to freeload. These behaviors have caused strong controversy and discussion on social media. The report exposes these negative behaviors and calls on international students to establish correct concepts of renting and interpersonal communication.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
