<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Seducing - 标签 - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/seducing/</link>
    <description>Seducing - 标签 - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-cn</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/seducing/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UQ - Pete韦 骗炮骗钱骗感情</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/uq-pete-wei/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/uq-pete-wei/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[这个故事讲述了一个名叫Pete Wei的骗子，他用欺骗、骗钱、骗感情的手法骗取女性。他甚至会敲诈勒索，像一个社会败类一样。此外，他也读过预科，对深圳和澳大利亚的女性都有欺骗行为。这个故事揭示了欺骗、骗钱和骗感情的现代城市陷阱，提醒女性增强自我保护意识。]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - 布里斯班商科渣女的时间管理秘诀</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[这篇文章揭示了一个UQ商科19岁渣女的时间管理秘诀。她精通于完美控制与她的两个男朋友之间的时间关系。她可以在两个男人之间相互转换，并能准确地处理好这两个男人的时间平衡。她的管理经验可以帮助你成为一名时间管理大师，在你的日常生活中更好地处理你的时间。]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Soton - 孙*浩 英区没有爱情</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:02:51 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/soton-sun-mo-hao/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[本次事件的渣男某孙姓同学成功地诠释了“英国没有感情”这句话。如果不是梦境的提示，我们可能永远无法知道这位纯爱战士已经跌倒多少次。以下是聊天记录，也是男主丑陋嘴脸的证据。]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>USYD - 牛子战神 半夜牛牛攻击</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:19:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/usyd-genitalia-er/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[一系列聊天记录曝光了悉尼牛子哥在多名女性中的骚扰行为，牛子哥自称在多个不同领域具有专业技能，却经常变换自己身份和学历，对女性进行谎言和虚假承诺。同时，牛子哥还试图让有资源的男生拉他进悉尼富二代群，并自称在美国有产业。此行径非常危险，应引起社会广泛关注。]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>TUoS - 阚博文 聊骚、欠钱、分手诋毁</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 10:12:29 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/tuos-kan-bowen/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[在和阚博文交往的10个月里，作者遭遇了这位男子的种种折磨。阚博文向作者借钱并不断诋毁她，甚至在分手后之后对其进行攻击和恶意谣言；金钱方面，作者共为阚博文垫付了近10万人民币，并存在纠纷无法解决。本文揭露了阚博文的罪行和女友所受的伤害，探讨了这种侵害个人财产和精神健康的不道德行为。]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Luo Junzhe&#39;s multiple illegal behaviors exposed</title>
  <link>http://example.org/posts/uscd-david/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:11:06 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>作者</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/posts/uscd-david/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Luo Junzhe's multiple illegal and unethical behaviors have been exposed, including stealing roommates' cash and credit cards, abusing cats, hiring prostitutes, freeloading, overcharging everyone, etc. He also set up his friend's online banking account to regularly transfer money to him, which is illegal and fraudulent to his friend. He also secretly used game cheats to deceive in games.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
