<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>GOSSIP - Category - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/categories/gossip/</link>
    <description>GOSSIP - Category - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:33:14 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/categories/gossip/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UK - Exposing D&#39;s Lies and Slanders</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-cornwall-girl-d/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:33:14 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-cornwall-girl-d/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article comprehensively analyzes the lies and slanders of an ex-girlfriend, systematically exposing her acts of rumormongering, fraud, slander, etc., and responding to her accusations one by one to clarify the truth.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Sydney - Improper behaviors of  student A exposed</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/sydney-somebody-a/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:10:09 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/sydney-somebody-a/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes the improper behaviors of a Sydney high school student A, including maliciously spreading rumors, backstabbing classmates, not cherishing friendships and relationships. We should treat others' mistakes with understanding and patience, and encourage them to reflect on and correct their mistakes.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UoL - Qin Ziyue and His Brother: Sound Equipment, Clothes, Accommodation, and Friendship</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uol-qin-ziyue/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:34:50 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uol-qin-ziyue/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes a series of illegal acts committed by Qin Ziyue's brother and girlfriend, who are friends studying in London. They stole someone else's phone, posted unauthorized content on social media, and wore other people's valuable items without permission. In addition, they failed to return and damaged expensive clothing, but did not offer any form of compensation. The article also calls on victims to protect their property and rights, and not to suffer from illegal acts such as the arbitrary use of items and verbal abuse due to agreement or favoritism.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - Pete Wei scams for sex, money, and emotional manipulation.</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:59:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-pete-wei/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This story is about a man named Pete Wei, who is a fraudster. He uses deception, blackmail, and emotional manipulation to scam girls. He has even studied pre-university courses and has targeted girls in Shenzhen and Australia. This story reveals the modern urban pitfalls of deception and fraud, and serves as a reminder for girls to be more aware and protective of themselves.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UCSD - Infidelity scandal shocks campus</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:56:23 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/ucsd-lib-sex/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[At UCSD, a male student was caught having sex with a female classmate in the library bathroom by his girlfriend. His girlfriend found evidence of him cheating on multiple women, including women of different ages, positions, and identities, in his phone. She sent the evidence to multiple class groups, causing a stir on campus. The scandal involved a married and pregnant biology PhD student, a middle school teacher who is now studying at UCSD, various senior and junior sisters, foreign students, and many women who confessed in videos that they already had boyfriends.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UoB - Wang Tiange Cyberbullying, Slander, and Reckless Infringement</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uob-wang-tiange/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 23:27:17 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uob-wang-tiange/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes the unethical behavior of a 93-year-old woman who recklessly violates the privacy of others, spreads rumors, and is subjected to doxxing on the internet. The author, based on personal experience, describes how the woman used screenshots, posted photos on social media, and doxxing to harass others, causing tremendous psychological pressure and serious mental and physical harm to the victims. At the same time, this article calls for serious crackdowns on cyberbullying and slander to protect the legitimate rights and dignity of every individual.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>QUB - Tang Shengxiang, Prince Beffa, and the Record of a Playboy</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/qub-prince-slogan/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:44:07 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/qub-prince-slogan/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[A missing person notice led to the Queen's University Belfast landlord searching for Prince Beffa, who breached the contract and disappeared. Prince Beffa used deception and speculation to accumulate wealth, and had a notorious reputation. The record documents a series of events, including his story with his (ex-)girlfriend. Due to the girlfriend leaving her passport and reporting to the police, the police were called multiple times. Prince Beffa's poor English couldn't explain things clearly, and the police took him away.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UQ - Brisbane Business School girl&#39;s time management secrets</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 20:26:04 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uq-scape-merivale-girl/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article reveals the time management secrets of a 19-year-old girl from UQ Business School who is skilled in perfectly controlling the time relationship between her two boyfriends. She can switch between the two men and accurately balance their time. Her management experience can help you become a time management master and better handle your time in your daily life.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UoE - The unknown truth about Zhang Qihang</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uoe-vincent/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:59:16 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uoe-vincent/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[An ex-girlfriend exposed the behavior of international student Zhang Qihang during and after their relationship on social media. The inappropriate behavior exposed includes disrespectful language, greed for the girlfriend's money, and a lack of seriousness towards gifts. The article also describes the rebellious actions of success-oriented Zhang Qihang in retaliation against his ex-girlfriend, causing attention and discussion in society.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UK - Chen Bangrui&#39;s exceptional time management skills and emotional manipulation</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-chen-bangrui/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:25:28 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uk-chen-bangrui/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[The girl in the article developed feelings for Chen Bangrui during their six-month relationship, but was informed by him one night that he had a girlfriend in the UK and asked her to fly to the UK to be with him immediately. After being deceived, she was attacked on the phone by a stranger and fell into pain and despair. The article also includes a conversation record with the girlfriend.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
