<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Violence - Tag - 瓜田 New</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/tags/violence/</link>
    <description>Violence - Tag - 瓜田 New</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:04:10 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/tags/violence/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
  <title>UM - Demon King accused of misconduct, but allegations are questionable</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:04:10 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/um-demon-king/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article describes a Melbourne University student, Demon King, who has been accused of multiple violations, including physical assault and traffic violations. However, the allegations are questionable, and some descriptions are false. The origin and authenticity of the article have been questioned, causing a lot of controversy.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>NYU - Wang Zicong Multiple Accusations (Fraud, Abuse, Deception)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-wang-zicong/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 13:57:35 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/nyu-wang-zicong/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[Multiple accusations have been made against a man named Wang Zicong, including fabricating virtual friends to scam money, abusing pets, slandering ex-girlfriends, spreading rumors about abortions, and threatening domestic violence. In addition, he enjoys engaging in various illicit activities such as leaking girls' private photos and secretly filming them. His crimes are serious and require legal sanctions and punishment.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>UoN - Xie Jun&#39;s Love Experience and the &#34;Light and Dark&#34; Plot</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/uon-xie-jun/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 21:18:33 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/uon-xie-jun/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article details the love experience between international students Lulu and Xie Jun, including Xie Jun's unreliable identity fraud, hypocrisy, and PUA behavior. The content also covers Xie Jun's concern over material items, selfishness, and the physical and psychological violence that caused Lulu's mental harm, helping readers understand the lives of international students in a foreign country.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
  <title>YU - Chen Yu Jian (Domestic Violence, Hypocrisy, PUA)</title>
  <link>http://example.org/en/posts/yu-chen-yujian/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:07:11 &#43;0800</pubDate>
  <author>Author</author>
  <guid>http://example.org/en/posts/yu-chen-yujian/</guid>
  <description><![CDATA[This article exposes a modern love tragedy that comes at the cost of false promises. The girl was deceived into a trap by a married man. The story she describes is full of pain and heartbreak, as she has been forgiving of him but he only cares about his own feelings. The behavior of a married man has caused her to experience domestic violence and emotional harm. This story is poignant because many people have similar experiences in real life. This article provides a reflective thinking, revealing the inequality and intricate emotional web in modern male-female relationships.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
